ghettogaggers.com 2015-03-15

# Customer Support Center - Privacy Statement

### Privacy Notice:

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your personal information is collected and used. A link to this notice can be found on every page and website within our network. 

### The Information We Collect:

Each time you visit any one of the DE Multimedia Ltd. websites, we will collect your host / IP address, cookies, and a record of the website which referred you. 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on DE Multimedia Ltd. operated websites. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

First Name:  
Last Name:  
Address:  
E-mail address:  
Phone number:  
State/Province:  
Country:

We DO NOT collect billing information, such as credit card numbers.

### The Way We Use Information:

DE Multimedia Ltd. collects account registration information on its web site. This is done to help us provide our visitors and clients with the best service and with valuable information regarding relevant products and services from DE Multimedia Ltd. and appropriate third parties. DE Multimedia Ltd. is always dedicated to protecting personal information and will make every reasonable effort to handle collected information appropriately. All relevant information collected, as well as related requests, will be handled as carefully and efficiently as possible in accordance with DE Multimedia Ltd.'s standards for integrity and objectivity. 

### Our Commitment To Data Security:

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Have a question? Contact Support!

Have something to say? Then please leave some feedback!
